准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
家庭派对
欢迎光临海绵宝宝的家庭派对
Welcome to "SpongeBob's House Party"
东道主是  海盗派斯
with your host, Patchy the Pirate
派对里有潘趣酒
There'll be punch
饼干  爆炸
cookies, explosions
以及海绵宝宝的全新剧集
and a brand-new episode of SpongeBob SquarePants
万岁
Hooray
加利福尼亚恩斯诺现场直播
Now, live from Encino, California
有请东道主海盗派斯给大家热情拥抱
get ready for a warm embrace
派对这边请
from our party host, Patchy the Pirate
滚开我家草坪
Get off my lawn
派对
Party?
这边没开派对
Geez, there ain't no party here
滚开
Go away
请进
Come on in
别吵  波蒂
Hush, Potty
看不出来我在赶流氓吗
can't you see I'm trying to keep out the riffraff?
流氓
Riffraff?
那是看电视的观众  缺心眼的
That's our television audience, barnacle-breath
还真是
Of course, it is
我刚刚闹着玩的
I was just fooling
欢迎光临
Welcome
你们没请海绵宝宝来参加派对吗
Say, you didn't bring SpongeBob with you, did you?
但愿他收到邀请函了
Gee, I sure hope he got his invitation
我是很想去参加派对
I'd sure like to go to this party
可我看不懂邀请函
but I can't read the invitation
我也是
Me, neither
送邀请函的那位肯定一点都不了解
Whoever sent this obviously has no idea
海底生活有多少物理限制
about the physical limitations of life underwater
还是都丢火里去吧
Well, might as well throw these in the fire
大家请进
Well, come on in
给大家介绍一下来宾
Let me introduce you around
这位是美人鱼米妮
This here's Minnie Mermaid
米妮跳舞跳太累  现在在纳凉
Minnie's cooling off on account of
she's been dancing her scales off
对不对啊  米妮
Isn't that right, Minnie, huh?
是在休息吗
Take a little breakie-poo?
不对  派斯
No, Patchy
其实我不待在水里就会没命
actually I'm in here because if I wasn't, I would die
这就对了
That's the spirit
来找找  你还不认识谁呢
Let's see, who else haven't you met?
这位是长胡子海盗
That's Longbeard, the Pirate
你好啊  长胡子
Hey there, Longbeard
好久不见
long time no see
谁这么大胆  敢打扰海神王
Who dares to interrupt Neptune?
抱歉  神哥
Sorry about that, Neppy
那位是海神王
That's Neptune
统治全海洋
He's king of the sea
你们玩得开心不
You kids having fun?
办派对可真是辛苦
Hosting a party is hard work, boy
这倒让我想起来
That reminds me
海绵宝宝办派对的那时候
of the time when SpongeBob was hosting a party
你们想看那集动画片吗
You kids want to see that cartoon?
你们想啊
You do?
那好  播动画片吧
Well, then, launch the cartoon
大闹派对
分镜总监
插曲分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
便宜货超市
啊  便宜货超市
Ah, the Barg'n Mart--
消费者的天堂
a consumer's paradise
放眼望去堆满了各种名牌仿品
of brand-like items stocked as far as the eye can see
19秒
19 seconds
破记录了  卢
That's a new record, Lou
太棒了  海绵宝宝
That's great, SpongeBob
一块四毛二
$1.42
不过想让它变成官方记录
But it's not an official record
得先把它记在记录册上面才行
until we record it in the Book of Records
记录册
19秒
"19 seconds"
好
Okay
总共一块四毛二
So it's $1.42
请在这边签名
Sign here, please
先是这边
Initial here
还有这边
And here
还有
And
这边
here
你看  是我第一次过来给你拍的照片
Look, it's a picture I took of you
the first time I ever came here
看看你  好年轻好快乐
Look at you, so young and happy
美好的时光渐行渐远到哪去了
Where do the years go?
那是什么
What's that?
动手办派对装备
"Plan Your Own Party Kit"
卢  要多少钱
Hey, Lou, how much?
是说动手办派对装备吗
For the Plan Your Own Party Kit?
现在买有优惠
We're having a special on those
免费
They're free
但你必须走了
But you have to leave
马上走
right now
来看看  小蜗
Let's see, Gary
动手办派对装备上面写着
According to the Plan Your Own Party Kit
首先一定要做邀请函
invitations are the first order of business
宾客名单要简短
"A short guest list
只请最亲近的熟人
"consisting of only your closest acquaintances
能为整晚奠定温馨基调
"will set an intimate tone for the evening
使得派对得以成功
and provide soirée success"
听见没  小蜗
You heard the man, Gary
只请最亲近的熟人
only our closest friends
到底谁是海绵宝宝
Who the barnacles is SpongeBob SquarePants?
想必你跟他是幼儿园同学吧  亲爱的
I believe you went to kindergarten with him, dear
珊瑚队加油
幼儿园吗
Kindergarten, huh?
贝壳老师班
没错  海绵宝宝
Oh, yeah, SquarePants
看来现在又得搬家了
Well, I guess it's time to move again
小蜗  这套动手办派对装备
Gary, this Plan Your Own Party Kit
帮上大忙了
is a real lifesaver
奶油乐
没它我怎么可能会知道
How else would I have known
一定要做新鲜的凝脂生奶油呢
to make freshly whipped clotted cream?
小蜗  快叫宇航员来
Gary, you better call an astronomer
因为我做的这凝脂奶油棒出地球了
because this clotted cream is out of this world
我的皮纳塔
My piñata
烫烫烫
Hot, hot, hot
动手办派对装备
The Plan Your Own Party Kit
要我装皮纳塔的时候得发挥创意
encourages creativity when stuffing your piñata
所以要装恶魔蛋  不装糖果
That's why I'm using deviled eggs
问得好  小蜗
Good question, Gary
不过你放心
but not to worry
动手办派对装备有警告说
The Plan Your Own Party Kit warns
派对不好好管理容易玩完
that unsupervised parties can lead to disaster
所以我才冒昧制定了一份时间表
That's why I've taken the liberty of devising a schedule--
八点到八点零五
8:00 to 8:05
客人抵达
guests arrive
八点零五到八点十五
8:05 to 8:15
开场白与综合讨论
opening remarks and general discussion;
八点十五到八点二十七
8:15 to 8:27
做手工
craft corner
并发放名牌
followed by name tag distribution
八点二十七分进行
At 8:27 we begin
吃饼干兼绕口令大赛的资格赛
the qualifying rounds
for our cracker-eating/ tongue-twister contest
九点零七  猜字谜
9:07, running charades
九点三十八  慈善咬苹果游戏
9:38, charity apple-bob
舞步
九点五十七  电子吉特巴舞马拉松
9:57, electric jitterbug dance marathon--
女生的不二之选
ladies' choice
十点零九  精彩一刻
At 10:09, things start cooking
那时我要开始做举世闻名的
as I dip into my world famous
敲门笑话撑杆跳
knock-knock joke vault
只要照着时间表上面的做
And as long as we stick to this schedule
派对保证成功
our party is a guaranteed success
这一定会是史上最酷派对了
This is going to be the coolest party ever
目前海绵宝宝的派对筹办得很顺利
Looks like it's smooth party sailing
for SpongeBob so far
现在换我来开派对了
Now it's time for me to get me own party underway
围过来  坏血病旱鸭子
Gather round, you scurvy landlubbers
一起来学幸福假腿舞
It's time to learn the Peg-legged Dance of Happiness
非常简单
It's quite simple really
只需要一根假腿  再多加耐心
All you need is a peg leg and some patience
另外买我的教学系列
and my instructional video series
只要二十九块九毛五
only $29.95
派斯舞蹈指南
立即下单
狂舞不止
只要二十九块九毛五
太俗气了
How tacky
原价可是要四十块的  波蒂
It's a $40 value, Potty, a $40 value
这舞非常好跳  非常好玩
Now, it's very easy and loads of fun
乐队到了
Hey, everybody, the band's here
乐队
Band?
什么乐队
What band?
我给派对雇来的乐队
The band I hired for the party
不错嘛  波蒂
A jolly idea, Potty
现场音乐让派对可以更热闹
A little live music'll get me shindig dug
哪个乐队  藤壶比尔与七大洋乐队吗
Who'd you get, Barnacle Bill and the Seven Seas?
不对
No
海草萨丽和她的爱笑海龟
Seaweed Sally and her cackling turtle?
不对
No
有了
I know--
大副兄弟
The First Mates
不对
No
盐水山姆
Salt Water Sam
特邀歌手有海水兄弟
featuring the Brine Brothers
不对
No
生锈铰链
Rusty Hinges
与关禁闭乐队
and the Boys from the Brig?
几年前早散伙了
They broke up years ago
那请的是哪个乐队
Well, who else is there?
鸟头乐队
The Bird Brains
鸟头乐队  比其他那堆乐队都强
The Bird Brains-- they're better than those other bands
可它们就只是群鸟
But they're just a bunch of birds
你好  恩斯诺
Hello, Encino
鸟头乐队
波蒂  刚刚那是我听过最难听的船歌
Oh, Potty, that's the worst sea chantey I've every heard
最好别吵上加吵
I certainly hope it doesn't get any louder
不行  不要
No, no
不准
No
别给我奏了
Stop the music
听我说
Look, boys
虽然你们的音乐就只有鸟会觉得好听
I know you fellas sound real good around the birdbath
但现在这是在电视直播
but this here is basic cable
现在这是重要时刻
This is the big time
恐怕你们现在得走甲板落海去了
I'm afraid it's time for you to walk the plank
你是说我们被解雇了吗
You mean we're fired?
错
No
快跳下去
Go on, start jumping
不然我就拿我剑刺你们
or you're going to be dealing
with the business end of me sword
不会吧
No
忘了你们是鸟了
I forgot that you're birds
请稍候
趁派斯还没平复情绪
While Patchy pulls himself together
来看看海绵宝宝的派对办得怎么样了
let's see how SpongeBob's party is shaping up
派对
开心玩
享用美食
小蜗  快准备好
Okay, Gary, get ready
就快八点了
it's almost 8:00
客人来了
Here they come
放心  小蜗
Don't worry too much, Gary
现在才八点零十秒钟
it's only ten seconds past 8:00
现在八点零二十秒
Now it's 20 seconds past 8:00
多半都没收到邀请函
Maybe nobody got their invitations
八点零三十秒了
30 seconds past 8:00
我完蛋了
I'm doomed
没一个来的
No one's coming
最烂东道主非我莫属
I'm the worst host ever
第一位客人来了
The first guest
才迟到了四十秒
and only 40 seconds late
嗨  海绵宝宝
Hi, SpongeBob
欢迎光临  派大星
Welcome, Patrick
我能不能夸你迟到得甚是光鲜亮丽
May I compliment you on being fashionably late?
要我给你打杯潘趣酒吗
Can I get you a glass of punch?
好
Sure
你路痴吗
Did you have any trouble finding the place?
喝吧
Here you are
谢了
Thanks
所以说潘趣酒行吗
So is the punch okay?
不错  不错
Not bad, not bad
天气还不错
Nice weather we're having
确实很温和
It's been very mild, yes
没错
Yep
这个季节就该温和
It's mild season
那  你看没看过
So, you read any?
派对又来几个客人
More party guests
欢迎光临  蟹老板
Welcome, Mr. Krabs
海绵宝宝好
Ahoy, SpongeBob
请让小蜗帮忙保管你的大衣
Please let Gary take your coat
然后由我来为你献上开胃菜
Then allow me to offer you some hors d'oeuvres
以及潘趣酒
and a glass of punch
不介意我就开吃了
Don't mind if I do
来了俩  还剩175个没来
Two down, 175 to go
宾客名单
差点给忘了
Gosh, I almost forgot
有这些名牌
These name tags
就用不着尴尬的自我介绍了
eliminate the need for awkward introductions
又来几个客人
More guests
星大派是我  子女尔人
"Kcirtap si eman ym o-77-eh"
你好  我是派大星
我看不懂
I don't get it
你个傻小子看错了  上面写的是
No, you dumb bunny, it says
你好  我是派大星
"Hello, my name is Patrick"
很高兴认识你  派大星
Nice to meet you, Patrick
真好笑  派大星
Good one, Patrick
对
Yeah
这怎么回事了
What's going on here?
九点零三分才安排大家笑
The laughter isn't scheduled until 9:03
要开派对就自家开去  派大星
You want to throw a party, do it at your house, Patrick
他是在跟你说话  还是跟我说话
Was he talking to me or you?
章鱼哥  你来了
Squidward, you made it
我电视坏了
My cable's out
我深表遗憾
Sorry to hear about that
所以说
So, uh
你好吗  章鱼哥
how's it going, Squidward?
不错
Not bad
我给你跟蟹老板安排了轻松对话
I have you making light conversation with Mr. Krabs
但仅限十点四十一到十点四十七
from 10:41 to 10:47
不过要是你非得急着说话
But if you've got a case of the jabber-jaws
现在就能给你把聊天对象改成史酷特
I can pair you up right now with Scooter
这是破冰用的话题卡
Here are some topic cards to break the ice
门口来客了
Someone's at the door
我的卡上写
Mine says
先有牡蛎  还是先有珍珠
"Which came first, the oyster or the pearl?"
你支持珍珠
You take the side of the pearl
太烂了吧
This is lame
我的卡上写
My card says
探讨讽刺的哲学本质
"Discuss the philosophical nature of irony"
你的卡上写什么
What does yours say?
礼貌点头
Nod politely
你的上面写什么  痞老板
What does yours say, Plankton?
对了  上面写
Yes, it says
你要说
你从哪里来
讨论蟹黄堡秘方的神秘配料
"Discuss the secret ingredient
of the Krabby Patty formula"
真有意思
How interesting
你想得美  痞老板
Nice try, Plankton
总算来了
Well, it's about time
全体成员  最后一位客人的抵达时间
Okay, everyone, the final guest is about to arrive
迟到22分钟了
22 minutes late
薯片
大家请注意
Attention, everyone
都注意了
Attention, please
既然都到齐了  那我正式宣布
Now that we're all here, I officially declare
派对正式启动
the party switch to be in the "on" position
万岁
Hooray
好耶
all right
好
okay
等我在更衣室里换完衣服回来
As soon as I get back from the coatroom
就来介绍今晚安排的活动
we'll have a rundown of tonight's scheduled events
大衣保管处
别丢下我就开玩了
Try not to have too much fun without me
说真的
Seriously
你们也一样哦
That includes you folks
海绵宝宝
家庭派对
海绵宝宝的家庭派对
"SpongeBob's House Party"
广告过后马上回来
will be right back after these messages
大家好
Ahoy, there
海绵宝宝
家庭派对
欢迎回到  海绵宝宝的家庭派对
Welcome back to "SpongeBob's House Party"
派对
小费
小蜗  我又给你找了件大衣
Hey, Gar, got another coat for you
顺带一提  派对一定会特好玩
The party's going great, by the way
一定会成为大家长期长期讨论的话题
They're going to be talking
about this one for a long, longtime
回去干活了
Well, back to "work"
全体成员  来
Okay, everybody, let's
怎么回事
What's going on here?
都乱套了
This is all wrong
我派对是怎么了
What's happening to my party?
不行不行
No, no
不行不行不行
no, no, no
没看时间表吗
Didn't you read the schedule?
晚上十点  狂舞不止
"10:00 pm: Dance your pants off"
晚上十点
10:00 pm
照着时间表上面玩  行不行
Let's try to stick to the schedule, shall we?
八点五十二分才吃光蛋糕
Cake will be eaten at 8:52, everyone
八点五十二
8:52
吹
吸
这什么东西
What's this?
是我的早餐
That's my breakfast
大家可不可以看过来
Could I have everyone's attention, please?
派大星
Patrick
大家往沙发上坐好  让我妥善安排
If everyone could take a seat
on the couch while I sort this out
谢谢配合  谢谢
Thank you, thanks
非常感谢大家耐心等候
Hey everybody, thanks for your patience
众所周知  万事开头难
I know we've gotten off to a rocky start here
所以我要带大家重回正轨
so I'm going to get us back on track
现在八点三十七了
It is now 8:37
都知道什么意思吧
and we all know what that means
来念报纸漫画
Time to read aloud from the newspaper comics
漫画
好像还
Sounds like a
挺刺激
real thrill
找找看  就先开始念小聪明一族吧
Let's see, I think I'll start out with "The Wisenheimers"
好  版面一
Okay, panel one
小聪明罗克西在使某种耙子
we see Roxy Wisenheimer with some sort of rake
等一下  这我不能念
Wait, I can't read from this
这张是昨天的报纸
This is yesterday's paper
我去拿今天的报纸
I'll just grab today's paper
海绵宝宝  你可太会开派对了
SpongeBob, you sure know how to throw a party
客人没我还能怎么办
What would they do without me?
锁外面了
Locked out?
这首歌节拍真棒
This song's got a great beat
是啊
Yeah--
咚咚咚
"knock, knock"
不知道为什么里面的都听不到
Gee, I wonder why they don't hear me
不会吧
Oh, no
里面的都没用话题卡
They're not using the topic cards
都在
They're
即兴创作
ad-libbing
这下派大星成众矢之的了
Now they're mad at Patrick
他在狂吃恶魔蛋
He's hogging the deviled eggs
看看那些可怜的灵魂
Look at those poor souls
一定无聊到快疯了
They're so bored they've gone mad
不会吧
Oh, no
派对都乱成一锅粥了
The party's falling into chaos
全怪我东道主没能带大家回正轨
without my hosting talents to guide it
那
So
你常来吗
do you come here often?
没
No
喂  海绵宝宝家
Hello, SquarePants residence
什么
What?
对不起  说什么
I am sorry, what?
电话
派大星  是我
Patrick, it's me
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你想找海绵宝宝啊
You want to talk to SpongeBob?
没错
Yeah
不对  派大星
No, Patrick
我就是海绵宝宝
I'm SpongeBob
就在外面
I'm outside
先别挂啊
Okay, hold on
海绵宝宝  你在外面吗
SpongeBob, are you out here?
有电话找你
Phone's for you
什么
Wha
我
I
派大星  你先别
No, Patrick, wait
抱歉  他不在外面
Sorry, he's not out there
兄弟  你找海绵宝宝
Hey, dude, if you're looking for SpongeBob
就去潘趣酒碗那边
he's over by the punchbowl
谢谢
Thanks
电话给你  海绵宝宝
Here you go, SpongeBob
找你的
it's for you
把电话放潘趣酒碗里
Phone in punchbowl?
根本就没列入时间表
That's not even on the schedule
帅哥拉里  你可真是秀色可餐
Larry, my man, you are looking good enough to eat
好耶  宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby
不过得涂点牙齿增白剂了
Could use a little teeth-whitener, though
海绵宝宝肯定不介意
I'm sure SpongeBob won't mind
他梳子长得也太怪了
Check out his crazy comb
不会吧  好像有谁
Oh, no, sounds like someone's
在翻我药箱
rummaging through my medicine cabinet
希望那谁别碰我的特制梳子
I hope they don't touch my special comb
通风得也差不多了
Well, I guess I've aired it out enough
派对终于开始精彩了
This party's finally starting to pick up
希望影响不到
I hope this doesn't interfere
九点二十的手指玩偶剧场
with finger-puppet theater at 9:20
要是没法进去恢复秩序
If I don't get back inside and restore order
多半就没时间办安排的活动了
there might not be time for any of the scheduled events
海绵宝宝也太会开派对了吧
Gee, SpongeBob really knows how to throw a great party
没错
Oh, yes
东西都很可爱
Everything is quite lovely
不过他的画作品味我可不喜欢
Although I don't care for his taste in paintings
我都不知道怎么会那样
I don't even know how that happened
那看来也没得选了
Well, I guess I have no choice
一定要挖地道进去
I'm going to have to tunnel back in
大家别怕
Okay, everybody, don't panic
东道主回来了
The host has returned
跳跳跳
Hop, hop, hop
虽说我还能接受不用话题卡
I can take losing the topic cards
还让电话放潘趣酒里的事
and the phone in the punchbowl
但本来应该是我要带头兔兔跳的
but I was supposed to lead the bunny hop
烂到不能再烂了
This is a bunch of barnacles
我要闯进去
I'm breaking in
好啊好啊
Well, well
看看这是谁
What do we have here?
抢匪兔兔
A burglar bunny
你说作案动机是啥呢  奥马利
Why do they do it, O'Malley?
不知道
I don't know
多半是以此为乐
It's probably how he gets his kicks
你这种罪犯让我想吐
You criminals make me sick
我没犯罪
I'm no criminal
我就住这
I live here
我
I
我只是在开派对
I'm just throwing a party
我真的被锁在门外了
I got locked out, I swear
那你怎么不早说
Well, why didn't you say so?
误会可大了
What a terrible misunderstanding
祝你派对愉快  先生
You have a nice party now, sir
刚刚我差点就以为
Boy, for a second there I thought
我会因为私闯我家被逮捕呢
I was going to be arrested
for breaking into my own house
突然来个那样的反转也太好笑了
What an ironic twist that would have been
先等一下
Wait a second
你开派对
If you're throwing a party
怎么不邀请我们
why weren't we invited?
可我
But I
你们
you, uh
都不知道你们
I didn't know you'd
动手办派对装备没说要
Plan Your Own Party Kit didn't mention
警察
the police
这么爱说就跟法官说去
Okay, motor-mouth, tell it to the judge
不行
Oh, no
手铐坏了
These cuffs are broken
手套坏了就不能押他坐牢了
We can't bring him in in broken cuffs
车上有副旧的还能用
I got an old pair in the car we can use
现在给你们打潘趣酒还来得及吗
Is it too late to offer you some punch?
先生  你有权保持沉默
Sir, you have the right to remain silent
自己冷冰冰地整晚坐大牢
All night in a stony lonesome
还得穿着兔兔装
in a bunny outfit
啊对  门锁上了
Oh, yeah, the door's locked
你好
幸好我就把备用钥匙放在
Good thing I keep a spare key under
垫子
the
下面
mat
看看这地方
Look at this place
派对已经烂完了
This party was a complete disaster
那可是我们大家参加过最棒的派对了
That was the greatest party any of us have ever been to
是吗
It was?
毫无疑问
Without a doubt
你是史上最佳派对东道主
you are the best party-thrower ever
是吗
I am?
没错
Yeah
你得把你的所作所为都记下来
Whatever you did, you should write it down
下周末再来一遍
and do it again next weekend
再次谢谢你  海绵宝宝
Thanks again, SpongeBob
再见
See ya
海绵宝宝
SquarePants
你又成功了
you've done it again
到头来我还是挺会办派对的嘛
I guess I know how to throw a party after all
小蜗
Gary
看来你玩得可开心了
Well, it looks like you had a good time
晚安  小蜗
Good night, Gary
很高兴能看到
I'm glad to see
海绵宝宝的派对圆满成功了
old SpongeBob's party worked out
现在该我来办我自己的派对了
Now I got to get me own party going
波蒂  准备好听听真正的音乐没
Potty, are you ready for some real music, huh?
准备好了
Okay, ready
我这种人不能得坏血病
Scurvy ain't for the likes of me
该你来长笛独奏了
It's time for your flute solo
谢了  波蒂
Thank you, Potty
差点忘了
I almost forgot
先等一下
Wait a minute
我不吹长笛
I don't play a flute
我吹的是横笛
I play a fife
波蒂  不要
Potty, no
居然没被炸死
I can't believe I survived that one
波蒂  救命
Potty, help me
女士们先生们  鸟头乐队
Ladies and gentlemen, The Bird Brains
鸟头乐队
一起来到我最爱的乐园
Come with me to the land I love
地址不在这
It's not right here
也不在街边和天上
down the street or up above
就在蔚蓝海洋最深处
It's down below in the deep blue sea
海绵宝宝住在这  大家一起乐逍遥
Where SpongeBob lives and the fun is always free
欢乐
下下下
Down, down, down
潜到海洋最深处
To the bottom of the sea
海绵宝宝就在这儿
Where our salty friend SpongeBob
等着你和我
Waits for you and me
下下下
Down, down, down
大家一起乐逍遥
Ah, we'll have lots of fun
你和我永远沐浴在海底阳光下
You and me forever in the underwater sun
大家如果有机会  就来捉水母
We'll catch some jellyfish if we get a chance
跟派大星打招呼  美美跳个舞
Say hello to Patrick and do a little dance
你好
跟珊迪打空手道
Karate-chop Sandy
看章鱼哥晒日光浴
See Squid get a tan
来吃一个蟹黄堡
Eat a Krabby Patty
阻止痞老板的诡计
And foil Plankton's plan
邪恶诡计
下下下
Down, down, down
潜到海洋最深处
To the bottom of the sea
会合海绵宝宝  和他的蜗牛小蜗
We'll hook up with SpongeBob and his snail, Gary
下下下
Down, down, down
大家一起乐逍遥
Oh, we'll have lots of fun
你和我永远沐浴在海底阳光下
You and me forever in the underwater sun
海底阳光下
Underwater sun
非常好
Great job, boys
感谢大家到来
Thanks for stopping by
出门可别让舷窗给撞到了
Don't let the porthole hit you on the way out
也感谢你们的到来
And thank you for stopping by
让这场派对乐趣加倍
You made this party a real fun time
辣妹们来了
The ladies are here
有辣妹
Ladies?
那可太好了
Shiver me timbers
欢迎辣妹们
Welcome, girlies
不要
No
再见了
Bye, folks
要找就找波蒂去
It's Potty you're after
别亲了
Stop with the kissing
感谢大家光临
And thank you for coming
海绵宝宝
家庭派对
海绵宝宝的家庭派对
to "SpongeBob's House Party"
别给我亲了
Belay the smooching